A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 8 FA1416
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Alexander P. Auchus, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4771)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Ellen Binder, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4772)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Neil Binkley, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4773)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Ashley I. Bush, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4774)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Richard M. Camicioli, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4775)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Ted M. Dawson, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4776)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Meika A. Fang, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4777)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Barry Gumbiner, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4778)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, David M. Holtzman, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4779)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Dalane W. Kitzman, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4780)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Peter F. Klein, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4781)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Edward H. Koo, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4782)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Harlan M. Krumholz, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4783)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Mark S. Lach, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4784)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Wayne C. Levy, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4785)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Frank M. Longo, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4786)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Richard A. Marottoil, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4787)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Greer M. Murphy, Jr., 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4788)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Lina M. Obeid, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4789)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Karen M. Prestwood, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4790)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Peter Reaven, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4791)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, May J. Reed, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4792)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Norman Relkin, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4793)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Ronenn Roubenoff, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4794)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Alan R. Shuldiner, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4795)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Joan M. Teno, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4796)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Mark H. Tuszynski, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4797)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, peter V. Vaitkevicius, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4798)
- Paul Beeson Physician Faculty Scholars in Aging Research Program, Lisa L. Von Moltke, 1994-1995 (Box 651, Folder 4799)
- Grants, The American Society of Nephrology, Fourth International Congress of Nephrology, 1968-1969 (Box 652, Folder 4800)
- Grants, Buffalo General Hospital, Application of Hemodialysis Procedure to Clinical and Investigative Problems, 1963-1966 (Box 652, Folder 4801)
- Grants, Buffalo General Hospital, Clinical Dialysis Research and Laboratory Studies in Application of the Dialyzer-blood Oxygenator Pump, 1959-1962 (Box 652, Folder 4802)
- Grants, Buffalo General Hospital, Development of a Therapeutic Engineering Unit to Design and Fabricate Biological Research and Clinical Apparatus, Labor-Saving Bedside Devices and Electronic Monitors, 1958-1961 (Box 652, Folder 4803)
- Grants, Buffalo General Hospital, Divided Renal Function Studies Utilizing Digital Renal Autofluoroscopy, 1965-1970 (Box 652, Folder 4804)
- Grants, Buffalo General Hospital, Investigation of Clinical Use of Blood Dialysis in Patients With Acute and Chronic Renal Diseases and in Certain Diseases Involving Hepatic and Cardiac Dysfunction, 1956-1959 (Box 652, Folder 4805)
- Grants, Children's Hospital Medical Center, Investigations Related to Cardio Vascular Surgery Under Hyperbaric Conditions, 1968-1970 (Box 652, Folder 4806)
- Grants, Children's Memorial Hospital, Study of Urinary Tract Malformations in Children, 1962-1970 (Box 652, Folder 4807)
- Grants, Children's Memorial Hospital, Urinary Incontinence, 1970-1973 (Box 652, Folder 4808)
- Grants, Cleveland Clinic Hospital, Continuous and Intermittent Continuous Dialysis for Treatment of Patients with Chronic Renal Failure, 1961-1964 (Box 652, Folder 4809)
- Grants, Cleveland Clinic Hospital, Dialysis Treatment of Patients with Chronic Renal Failure, 1964-1971 (Box 652, Folder 4810)
- Grants, Deaconess Hospital, Clinical and Experimental Studies in Hemodialysis and the Development of a Board Artificial Kidney Research and Clinical Dialysis Program, 1959-1962 (Box 652, Folder 4811)
- Grants, Georgetown University, A Study of Factors Affecting Allogenic and Xenogenic Transplantation Tolerence, 1969-1974 (Box 652, Folder 4812)
- Grants, Georgetown University, A Study of Renal and Electrolyte Physiology and Clinical Research in Acute and Chronic Renal Insufficiency, Dialyzable Poisons, Nephrotic Syndrome, Pyelonephritis and Other Organic Renal Diseases, 1960-1961 (Box 652, Folder 4813)
- Grants, Health Research, Inc., Transplantation Antigens, 1968-1976 (Box 652, Folder 4814)
- Grants, The Hospital for Sick Children, Experimental and Clinical Studies of Hepatic and Renal Disease, 1965-1967 (Box 652, Folder 4815)
- Grants, Hospital of the University of Pennsylvania, 1961, 1964 (Box 652, Folder 4816)
- Grants, Hospital of the University of Pennsylvania, Preservation of Organs and Tissues, 1965-1975 (Box 652, Folder 4817)
- Grants, The Jefferson Medical College of Philadelphia, Development of Isolated Small Bowel Dialysis for Chronic Uremia, 1967-1970 (Box 652, Folder 4818)
- Grants, Loma Linda university School of Medicine, Studies on Effect of Electrophrosed Skin in Preventing Transplant Rejection, 1971-1973 (Box 652, Folder 4819)
- Grants, Lutheran General & Deaconess Hospitals, Hyperbaric oxygen Therapy, 1963-1971 (Box 652, Folder 4820)
- Grants, Massachusetts General Hospital, Development of an Artificial Urinary Sphincter, 1966-1968 (Box 652, Folder 4821)
- Grants, Minneapolis Medical Research Foundation, Inc., Basic and Clinical Hyperbaric Surgical Research, 1965-1972 (Box 652, Folder 4822)
- Grants, Minneapolis Medical Research Foundation, Inc., Study of Cardiac Assist by Hemodilution and Hyperbaric Oxygenation, 1968-1971 (Box 652, Folder 4823)
- Grants, North Carolina Baptist Hospitals, Inc., The Artificial Kidney in Clinical Medicine, 1959-1962 (Box 652, Folder 4824)
- Grants, North Carolina Baptist Hospitals, Inc., A Study of the Etiology and Prevention of Kidney Stone Formation, 1959-1968 (Box 652, Folder 4825)
- Grants, The Palo Alto Medical Research Foundation, A Study of the Nature of Gamma Globulins in Normal and Immunologically Inadequate Human Subjects, 1961-1968 (Box 653, Folder 4826)
- Grants, Passavant Memorial Hospital, The Artificial Kidney and Metabolic Studies in Renal Failure and Edema, 1958-1961 (Box 653, Folder 4827)
- Grants, Passavant memorial Hospital, Metabolic Abnormalities in Uremia, 1962-1964 (Box 653, Folder 4828)
- Grants, Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, Homotransplantation of Kidneys, liver, Skin, and Related Aspects of Intensive Care and Metabolism, 1963-1969 (Box 653, Folder 4829)
- Grants, Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, Investigation of Energy Sources and Their Metabolic Utilization Following Trauma and Surgery, 1961-1964 (Box 653, Folder 4830)
- Grants, Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, Multidiscipline Investigation of the Autogenous Immunologic Phenomena in Tissue Rejection and in the Autoimmune Diseases, 1961-1968 (Box 653, Folder 4831)
- Grants, Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, Studies of Intrarenal Blood Flow Distribution in a Man, 1967-1972 (Box 653, Folder 4832)
- Grants, Rhode Island Hospital, To Organize and Implement an Artificial Kidney Program, 1959-1963 (Box 653, Folder 4833)
- Grants, Royal Victoria Hospital, Isolation, Characterization and Clinical Evaluation of Naturally Occurring Antihistamines, 1967-1973 (Box 653, Folder 4834)
- Grants, Sacred Heart Hospital, To Establish a Community Center for Hemodialysis of Patients with Acute and Chronic Renal Failure and Certain Types of Dializable Poisonings, 1963-1964 (Box 653, Folder 4835)
- Grants, Scripps Clinic and research Foundation, Interaction of Viruses and Antibodies, 1967-1973 (Box 653, Folder 4836)
- Grants, Swedish Hospital, To Implement a Community Hemodialysis Center for Research and Treatment of Chronic Uremia and Terminal Renal Failure, 1961-1967 (Box 653, Folder 4837)
- Grants, Tulane University School of Medicine, New Methods of Diagnosis of Kidney Disease in Children, 1968-1970 (Box 653, Folder 4838)
- Grants, Tulane University School of Medicine, Renal Function in Children with Congenital Abnormalities, 1965-1968 (Box 653, Folder 4839)
- Grants, University Hospital of New York University Medical Center, The Relationship of Bacterial Antigens to Mammalian tissues with Special Reference to Problems in Autoimmune Diseases and Tissue Transplantations, 1965-1970 (Box 653, Folder 4840)
- Grants, University Hospital of New York University Medical Center, Tissue Typing Program, 1969-1972 (Box 653, Folder 4841)
- Grants, University of Oregon Medical School, The Production of Immune Tolerance in Humans, 1965-1972 (Box 653, Folder 4842)
- Grants, University of Washington School of Medicine, A Basic and Applied Medical Engineering Study of the Process of Hemodialysis, 1964-1965 (Box 653, Folder 4843)
- Grants, University of Washington School of Medicine, A Basic and Applied Medical Engineering Study of the Hemodialysis Process with Emphasis on the Technique and Logistics of Home Dialysis, 1965-1969 (Box 653, Folder 4844)
- University of Florida, Pathology of Cadaveric Renal Allograft, 1969, 1979 (Box 653, Folder 4845)
- Photographs, American Academy of Pediatrics, Annual Report 1983 (Box 654, Folder 4846)
- Photographs, American College of Physicians, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 4847)
- Photographs, American Lung Association, 1983 (Box 654, Folder 4848)
- Photographs, Blue Cross/Blue Shield of Greater New York, Health Services Improvement Fund, Inc., 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4849)
- Photographs, Boston University, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 4850)
- Photographs, Business of Health, Annual Report 1983 (Box 654, Folder 4851)
- Photographs, Center for Policy Studies, Walter McClure, Annual Report 1983, 1984 (Box 654, Folder 4852)
- Photographs, Commonwealth Health Care Corporation, 1983 (Box 654, Folder 4853)
- Photographs, Community Services Society of New York, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4854)
- Photographs, Hartford Fellows, Annual Report 1983, 1984 (Box 654, Folder 4855)
- Photographs, Hartford Geriatric Faculty Development Awards, Annual Report 1983, 1984 (Box 654, Folder 4856)
- Photographs, Harvard medical School Department of Radiology, Barbara McNeil, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 4857)
- Photographs, Health Services Foundation, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4858)
- Photographs, HealthChoice, Inc., Annual Report 1983, 1984 (Box 654, Folder 4859)
- Photographs, InterStudy, Annual Report 1983, 1984 (Box 654, Folder 4860)
- Photographs, Johns Hopkins University, Center for Hospital Finance & Management, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4861)
- Photographs, Johns Hopkins University, Energy Program, Annual Report 1983, 1984 (Box 654, Folder 4862)
- Photographs, Manhattan Eye, Ear, & Throat Hospital, 1982-1983 (Box 654, Folder 4863)
- Photographs, Massachusetts General Hospital (Box 654, Folder 4864)
- Photographs, Maternity Center, 1975-1976, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4865)
- Photographs, Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 654, Folder 4866)
- Photographs, National Executive Service Corps (NESC), 1983 (Box 654, Folder 4867)
- Photographs, National Governors' Association, 1983 (Box 654, Folder 4868)
- Photographs, New York Hospital, Cornell Medical Center, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4869)
- Photographs, Northern Sierra Hospital Council, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4870)
- Photographs, Ohio State University, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4871)
- Photographs, Palo Alto Medical Foundation, 1983 (Box 654, Folder 4872)
- Photographs, Philadelphia Geriatric Center, 1984 (Box 654, Folder 4873)
- Photographs, Presbyterian Hospital in the City of New York, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4874)
- Photographs, Providence Medical Center, 1981-1982 (Box 654, Folder 4875)
- Photographs, Rutgers, College of Medicine and Dentistry, 1982-1983 (Box 654, Folder 4876)
- Photographs, St. Luke's-Roosevelt Hospital, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4877)
- Photographs, Santa Barbara County Department of Health, 1981-1982 (Box 654, Folder 4878)
- Photographs, SHARE, Generic HMO, Annual Report 1983, 1984 (Box 654, Folder 4879)
- Photographs, South Florida Health Action Coalition, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4880)
- Photographs, University of California San Francisco, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4881)
- Photographs, University of Washington, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 4882)
- Photographs, Yale University, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 4883)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1981, Releases, 1982 (Box 655, Folder 4884)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1984 (Box 655, Folder 4885)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1985 (Box 655, Folder 4886)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1988, 1989 (Box 655, Folder 4887)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1989, 1989-1990 (Box 655, Folder 4888)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1990, 1989-1991 (Box 655, Folder 4889-4890)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1991, 1991-1992 (Box 655, Folder 4891)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1992, 1993 (Box 655, Folder 4892)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1992, Don Battershall, 1992-1993 (Box 656, Folder 4893)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1993 (Box 656, Folder 4894)
- Photographs, Annual Report 1994, 1995 (Box 656, Folder 4895)
- Photographs, Release Forms, 1991 (Box 656, Folder 4896)
- John A. Hartford Foundation Bulletin, 1983 (Box 656, Folder 4897)
- Guided Care, A New Nurse-Physician Partnership in Chronic Care, 2009 (Box 656, Folder 4898)
- Transformation: A Family's Guide to Chronic Care, Guided Care and Hope, Tom Grunder, 2010 (Box 656, Folder 4899)
- John A. Hartford Foundation Audiovisual Materials, 1
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research. When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  Individual items, including those that are not available in modern formats, may be restricted at the discretion of RAC.
  Sound recordings; Moving Images
  - Workshop on Small Employer Collective Purchasing - Tape 1, circa1990s; 2017:003:008; VHS; 75 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11711)
    Related Materials
    FA1416, Series 8, Box 647 Folder 4737 Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Miscellaneous
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instructions.
  - Workshop on Small Employer Collective Purchasing - Tape 2, circa1990s; 2017:003:009; VHS; 113 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11712)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Workshop on Small Employer Collective Purchasing - Tape 3, circa1990s; 2017:003:010; VHS; 62 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11713)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact an RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Tape A: Moving Beyond the Rhetoric: Putting Health Purchasing into Alliances Action "Key Purchasing Alliance Design & Implementation Issues for States" "The Promise of HPAs for Addressing America's Health Access & Cost Problems", 1993; 2017:003:011; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11714)
    FA1416, Box 647 Folder 4737 Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Miscellaneous
  - Tape B: Moving Beyond the Rhetoric: Putting Health Purchasing into Alliances Action "Choosing & Designing Purchasing Alliances" "The Role of HPAs Relative to Health Planning, Public Health & Prevention", 1993; 2017:003:012; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11715)
  - Tape C: Moving Beyond the Rhetoric: Putting Health Purchasing into Alliances Action "Purchasing Alliance as Ombudsman" "State of the Art Information for Oversight & Management of HPAs", 1993; 2017:003:013; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11716)
  - Tape D: Moving Beyond the Rhetoric: Putting Health Purchasing into Alliances Action "Encouraging the Development of Integrated Health Plans" "Accountable Health Plan Perspectives", 1993; 2017:003:014; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11717)
  - Tape E: Moving Beyond the Rhetoric: Putting Health Purchasing into Alliances Action "Selecting & Negotiating with AHPs: How Proactive Should Purchasing Alliances Be" "How Do We Get There From Here? Strategies for Transition & Implementation", 1993; 2017:003:015; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11718)
  - Community Health Management Information System (CHMIS), Washington State, A Working Example, 1993; 2017:003:019; VHS; 11 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11719)
  - Houston Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training, The Texas Five-Step Approach to Teamwork, 1998; 2017:003:007; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11720)
    Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training (GITT) Program, A Curriculm from the Huffington Center on Agining, Box 643 Folder 4705
  - PACE "Assessment Training Tape for Nurses", On Lok, Inc., 1991; 2017:003:002; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11721)
    On Lok senior Health Services, Geriatric Interdisciplinary Team Training, Jennie Chin Hansen (96203-G) Box 580 Folder 4294
  - MGMA: Strategies That Work - Part 1, 1997 October 28; 2017:003:003; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 7774)
  - MGMA: Strategies That Work - Part 2, 1997 November 4; 2017:003:004; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 7775)
  - Geriatric Session: M. Sager, MD; B. Kirkman-Fiff, DrPH, 1997 October; 2017:003:005; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 7776)
  - Geriatric Session: Enhancing Primary Care of Frail Elders, 1997 October; 2017:003:006; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 7777)
    Scope and Contents
    B. Kirkman-Liff, DrPH; C. Schraeder, PhD, RN; L. Sommers, DrPH; F. Williams, PhD
  - CHMIS Regional Presentations - 1, 1994; 2017:003:016; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 7778)
    Iowa, Memphis, Minneapolis, New York, Ohio - Seattle
  - CHMIS Regional Presentations - 2, 1994; 2017:003:017; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 7779)
    Ohio, Vermont, California, Colorado, Hawaii, Maryland, Michigan
  - CHMIS Regional Presentations - 3, 1994; 2017:003:018; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 7780)
    New Jersey, Rhode Island, Utah, West Virginia